(EP05 Behind-the-Scenes)
(Behind-the-Scenes 1)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Come on, teach me.
I'll teach you something simple.
Okay.
Wait.
You need to tell me a song
before I can teach you how to play it.
Any song you know.
Colorful Clouds Chasing the Moon?
Which part do you want to start with?
Okay.
(Demonstrating step by step)
Or...
(Focused)
For example.
It does slip around a bit.
Like this.
This part is a little tricky.
Is it these two fingers or these two?
Three, four.
Teach me how to sing.
You teach me how to sing.
Your teacher's right here.
Sing?
You're a vocal teacher.
I'm not.
"Genius".
That's what you call a "genius".
I'm already "off-key".
You pick it up just by watching.
"Help!"
That's great composition.
Great composition.
Yeah, great composition.
Sorry.
(Behind-the-Scenes 2)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Oh my gosh.
Wow.
Seriously.
I went
on a goodbye date today.
Yeah.
But honestly, I feel like
if this were your "movie",
this would be, like,
the first 30% of it.
It's just the first part of your story.
Once that little story ends,
that's when you start
to "transform".
And then, you know.
You become a better version of yourself
after a major change.
Yeah, and you become braver.
Now you can start following
the "main storyline".
Tell me how I'm supposed to do that.
Just do it normally.
Just be yourself.
Okay. We'll just be ourselves.
Yeah.
(Behind-the-Scenes 3)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
My shrink plastic sheets
finally arrived.
You bought so many.
There are only ten sheets.
(First attempt
at making shrink plastic failed)
Is it a problem with the paper?
(Realizing)
As expected, it's different.
Really?
(Feeling it)
I can really feel the difference.
Yeah.
You just saved the whole world.
How small can it shrink?
Can it shrink down to this size?
About that much.
It's okay. You can decide.
They both look good.
If you mess up...
we still have more.
There are plenty.
We've got plenty of backups.
Yeah.
(Starting to draw)
(Glances)
(Leaning closer)
(Giggling)
It feels so much more vibrant
than last time.
The paper you bought is better.
Why are you laughing?
I'm amazed you're so good with words.
You taught me.
Little by little.
You must be a really fast learner.
I take learning seriously.
(Behind-the-Scenes 4)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
I loved watching
The Racing Brothers Let's & Go!!
as a kid.
I watched it too.
I even bought some of the toys.
Did you watch Balala the Fairies?
Not really. The thing is,
they had to go through
this long transformation
before every fight.
"Gunala, God of Darkness!"
(Laughs)
I don't get it.
"Woohoo Lahoo!"
"Dark Magic Transformation!"
I can't stand
these drawn-out transformations.
Did you ever think about
how Ultraman always waited
until the last second
to use their ultimate move?
Why couldn't they just use it
right away and finish the fight?
Why did they have to wait
until their light turned red,
then suddenly remember
they had this ultimate move?
Yeah, that light was always going
to turn red.
It's kind of like Pokemon.
Yeah.
Someone has to be near death
before you can unleash new power.
Maybe that's exactly why
we loved these shows so much as kids.
It's just that now that we're grown up,
we look at that part
and think it's ridiculous,
but also kind of hilarious.
Maybe I'm just childish,
but sometimes
I still get into that feeling.
Like, say your
when your teammate gets hurt,
and then suddenly...
You start spinning around to transform.
I wouldn't spin around
and transform before a fight.
Which Ultraman is your favorite?
(Asks)
I got into Ultraman with Tiga.
Tiga. Got it.
Back then, I was so...
Even now that I think about it,
I still feel like
it'd be hilarious if I told you.
You know?
Back then, I told my grandma
the two of us
should go out the next day.
She asked why.
I said I wanted to look
for the Sparklens.
Then she asked
where we were going.
I said we had to go to Yunnan.
She asked why.
I said the Sparklens was hidden deep
in the mountains.
It didn't just appear anywhere.
We have to go deep
into the mountains to find it.
(Behind-the-Scenes 5)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Describe the first impression
in one word.
One word? First impression?
(First Impression)
(Thinking)
How about this?
Two words.
One for the first impression,
(First & Current Impression)
and one for the current impression.
Sure.
A word that sums it all up.
Okay, I'm done.
I'm ready.
(Glances)
Is there anything you're curious about?
(First Impression: Shy.
Current Impression: Simple)
(Glances)
It doesn't seem that difficult.
Can you see this?
(Moving closer)
Sensitive.
(First Impression: Sensitive)
Steady.
(Current Impression: Steady)
Actually, when I first met you,
I thought
you were a sensitive person.
Why?
It was your eyes.
And all those little details.
You were observing everyone.
You noticed that?
(Grabbing)
You're pretty observant too.
And now, I think
you're steady.
Stable, basically.
You're calm and even-keeled.
You don't have many emotional
ups and downs.
That's how I see you now.
Actually, I'm still pretty curious.
Yesterday, on Chill Day, you said
you'd already thought about
what you'd say if I came up.
(Curious)
Honestly, I was thinking of saying...
You mentioned before
that you're pretty rational at work,
but maybe not as much in everyday life.
I actually hope that at work,
you can think
about yourself a little more.
(Nods)
That's it?
(Behind-the-Scenes 6)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Why are you taking pictures again?
(Hold it in place)
Come in.
Hi, everyone.
Hello.
Do you want a picture?
Come on, together.
Get ready. Let's take a picture.
Come on.
This should gradually fade out,
and then it'll flash once it's gone.
Okay, everyone?
Okay.
Over here?
Come on, we're ready.
Do you want to take off the blanket?
I'm not taking it off.
This is my outfit for today.
(Today's outfit)
Okay.
Okay, did you two in the back hear me?
Did you hear that?
Yes.
You two.
We can't have you two spread out.
You stay in the middle. That's fine.
Right in the middle.
Okay, that's good.
Okay, Fang, you need to show yourself.
Okay.
Hurry.
Come on.
We all look so good.
I'll go get some bread.
Okay.
(Glances)
I'll take a picture of you two.
Yu Yang, Fang.
Thanks. Should we pose like this?
We... My outfit today is really...
(Getting closer)
Pink and cute.
(Move over)
Three,
two,
one.
This looks amazing.
Thank you.
Thanks.
(Behind-the-Scenes 7)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
(Notices)
What's wrong with you?
I feel like I'm coming down with a cold.
Maybe it's because the weather
is a little cold today.
It's definitely cold today.
Come on, let's go back.
Let's go.
We'll head upstairs first.
Bye bye.
Bye.
(Stops)
(Comes closer)
Can you tell what I was trying to say?
What?
Good night.
(Good night)
You guessed it.
Did I?
Yeah.
Then let's...
Sit for a bit.
You can take some medicine.
(Worried)
I think I'll be fine
if I drink some hot water.
Still, you should take something
just in case.
Do you want some? I have cold medicine.
No, I'm fine. I don't get sick.
I rarely get sick.
Don't say that.
I haven't been to the hospital
in over a year.
I haven't taken any medicine either.
That's great.
I hope you never need to see a doctor
or take medicine.
This is my first time
wearing dark-colored clothes.
(Observing closely)
Then I have to make sure
I remember this.
I'll record it with my eyes.
(Behind-the-Scenes 8)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
My handwriting is really ugly.
I didn't practice
(Thinking)
as a kid.
It could use some work.
That's true.
That's a very tactful way to put it.
(Amused)
There's a lot of room for improvement.
I even studied calligraphy for a while.
But I really couldn't sit still.
My first class was just drawing circles
over and over.
Drawing circles
with a calligraphy brush.
Can you draw a perfect circle?
It doesn't matter
if your circle is perfect.
You just have to keep drawing.
You have to calm your mind.
But I feel like
you're actually pretty patient.
(Whispering)
When is our macaroni coming?
So embarrassing.
I'm still hungry.
It's okay.
I ordered it.
And you happened to want some,
so I'll share a little with you.
Yeah.
You ordered it.
(Behind-the-Scenes 9)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
This photo looks good.
It's also one of my favorites.
It's really good.
Xing.
I feel like this one
looks good too.
I like this one.
It really brings out your beauty.
(Laughs)
Okay.
(Caring)
Are you tired?
No, my eyes just feel a little dry.
Then I'll head inside.
Okay.
Go back and get some rest.
Xing, don't you have any eye drops?
It's okay.
(Concerned)
I'll take out my contact lenses later.
Okay, Xing.
Go back and get some rest.
Okay, then.
Bye bye.
Okay. Get some rest.
Bye.
(Behind-the-Scenes 10)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
(Offering)
How about I take a picture of you guys?
With this one?
You can drape it over yourself.
(Celebrity)
Like the celebrity
and a man draped in a blanket.
Like this. Come on.
(One hand in pocket)
Where should we go?
Where should we do it?
Where do you guys want?
By this frame.
We could take it by the blue flowers.
Sure, then let's do it here.
Sure.
Isn't that a little too far apart?
(Moves closer)
I'm trying to fit you all in the frame.
I'll take it from up here.
(Runs)
Then should we
stand on one side?
Come here.
Wow.
Oh my.
Wait.
Wow.
This is amazing, girl.
(Finding the angle)
How does it look?
Looks good.
You even winked.
Wow.
Who knew you had that in you?
Let's take one
that's a little funnier, okay?
Sure.
Sure, wait a second.
Three, two, one.
My expression.
(Behind-the-Scenes 11)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
(Glances)
(Fluent)
Wow.
(Shy)
(Grab)
(Raises hand at the same time)
You go ahead.
Here. That's right.
(Leans closer)
Like this.
I showed you once. Did you get it?
That's not right.
(Laughs)
Yes.
This is how the two of us play it.
Like two mice playing the piano.
I'll do it. I'll just do it myself.
(Sways)
(Follows)
Let's get moving.
(Behind-the-Scenes 12)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
(Leans closer)
Let me see.
Isn't it kind of chubby?
Let me take a look.
Not really.
Definitely.
But yeah,
you've definitely
gotten a lot thinner now.
Here, let me take a picture of you guys.
Okay.
Three,
two,
one.
Thanks, Meng.
Thanks.
It looks really good.
(Turning his head)
I was looking in the wrong place again.
Next time,
look at the top of the Polaroid.
That's where I always look.
The white part.
You're really skinny.
Look at you.
Of course.
"A pointed face".
My forehead.
What's wrong with your forehead?
I really can't stand my forehead.
Don't you like the heart shape?
It's such a perfect one.
Look at his forehead. It's a heart.
A heart shape.
You did your hair really well.
Yeah.
My hair is really full.
Here, touch it.
Touch it.
It is.
(Behind-the-Scenes 13)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
Do you prefer talking face-to-face
or sitting off to the side?
Face-to-face feels pretty different.
I can really see your expressions
and reactions.
I feel like
face-to-face is better when two people
are just getting to know each other.
Because when we're talking,
we can pick up on
the other person's
subtle reactions and expressions.
Do you usually like eating alone?
Yeah. I really need to break that habit.
Have you felt any differently
these past few days?
About Signal House?
I feel like I've completely adjusted
to this kind of lifestyle.
Do you have any allergies?
I might be lactose intolerant.
(Nods)
Do you have any allergies?
(Asks)
I don't think so. I'm pretty tough.
None at all?
I don't think I have any.
You don't have any dietary restrictions?
None.
(Behind-the-Scenes 14)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
When I first started watching tennis,
I watched the Australian Open.
And the court was this same blue color.
Badminton courts can be blue too.
Okay.
We can play when we get back
to Signal House.
(Invitation)
The badminton court downstairs? Okay.
Badminton looks really fun.
They're fun in different ways.
But in terms of how much
you have to move,
I feel like
it's about the same.
With badminton,
you probably know certain positions
and know how to move around.
Tell me about it.
Like, which positions?
(Curious)
In badminton,
you practice four-way footwork.
And when you play singles,
after you return a shot,
you need to get back to the center.
From the center,
you can reach anywhere fastest.
As for tennis,
I honestly don't know
how to play at all.
But I've played badminton before.
The coach said that wouldn't work.
He said the two
aren't the same thing.
But
they look so similar
that it's hard
not to associate the two.
Your body just reacts instinctively
and you end up returning it that way.
So I was thinking,
I guess I really do
need to properly
tell these two sports apart.
It's okay.
As long as we're having fun.
I think I'm having a lot of fun.
(Behind-the-Scenes 15)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
I'm going out for a bit.
Why?
I'll be right back.
Wait for me.
(Getting ready to go together)
It's okay.
No.
Stay here.
I have to...
No.
(Worried about Fang's foot)
I'll be right back.
You're going out to get medicine.
(Guessed right)
Stay here.
Okay?
(Pinch)
(Holding her up)
Watch your foot.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
(Heading out to get medicine)
(Arriving at the pharmacy)
Hi.
Do you have anything for pain?
It's just
that her toenail is slightly lifted.
Is there something to apply or take?
For something to take, ibuprofen.
(Carefully asking)
Is there anything to apply?
An anti-inflammatory.
But her toenail is lifted.
Can she apply it?
Yes, she can.
Then I'll take both.
Okay?
I want both.
Okay. Payment done.
Thanks.
(Back to Signal House)
You're finally back.
I'm back.
I already finished cleaning the kitchen.
You did chores again?
I had nothing else to do.
Are we staying here?
Sure.
(Hands over)
There's one to apply and one to take.
Okay.
Thanks.
No problem.
(Behind-the-Scenes 16)
(Behind-the-Scenes)
How about we take a break?
Sure.
Let's sit for a bit.
Yeah, let's sit.
We climbed a long way.
With how afraid of heights I used to be,
I wouldn't even dare sit like this.
I wouldn't let any part of my body
leave this platform.
Same here.
But you're much better now.
Yeah.
Your feet are already off the platform.
I'm just getting used to the height.
We're about to jump off it.
Did you ever imagine you could fly
when you were a kid?
(Curious)
I did. I used to imagine it.
You used to.
(Laughing)
You can really fly in a minute.
That's terrifying.
Chris.
Hi, Maria.
Maria.
Maria,
are you ready?
I'm not ready.
Then I'll wait until you are.
Are you ready?
I'm always ready.
Always ready.
Yeah.
=Heart Signal (China Version) S9=
(SVIP updates every Mon & Tue at noon)
(VIP episodes update every Tues at noon,
members get one-week early access.)